# TEDDY LAZEBNIK

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

Electronic Address: lazebnik.teddy@gmail.com

Mobile: +972-54-5524589 Marital Status: Married Birth Date: 14th July, 1997

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Mathematical models and algorithms researcher (and developer) in the fields of epidemiology, medical, economics, and information systems. Ten years experience in software development in the industry, including five years experience as an algorithm developer with a focus on data-driven algorithms for medical and biological tasks, and AI algorithms for natural language processing, computer vision, and graph-based optimization.

### ACADEMIC EDUCATION

# **Bar-Ilan University**

2013 - 2016

B.Sc. in Applied Mathematics

· Final project about "Observable of Discrete - continuous Linear Time Interval Systems with Continuous Time Measurement".

# Bar-Ilan University

2017 - 2018

M.Sc. in Applied Mathematics

· Thesis about "Highly Stable Numerical Algorithm for Matrix Exponent" (Hebrew) - supervised by Dr. Shlomo Yanetz.

#### **Bar-Ilan University**

2018 - 2021

Ph.D. in Computer Science

· Thesis about "Large Scale Medical Nanoparticles Pharmacokinetics Mathematical Modeling and Simulation" - supervised by Prof. Gal A. Kaminka and Dr. Hana Weitman.

## **Ariel University**

2020 - 2021

Ph.D. in Biomathematics

· Thesis about "Modeling and Numerical Calculation of COVID-19 spread and Optimal Oncology Treatment protocols" - supervised by Dr. Svetlana Bunimovich-Mendrazitsky.

#### ACADEMIC EMPLOYMENT

# Holon Institute of Technology (HIT), Department of Mathematics

Oct 2019 - Feb 2020

Teaching Assistant

· Teaching Numerical Analysis.

# Holon Institute of Technology (HIT), Department of Mathematics

Feb 2020 - July 2020

Lecturer

· Teaching Deep Learning for Computer Vision.

#### Bar-Ilan University, Department of Mathematics

Oct 2018 - July 2020

Research And Teaching Assistant

- · Teaching the following courses: partial differential equations (PDE), Introduction to linear mathematical optimization, Numerical Analysis 1, and Tools for Numerical Programming for Engineering.
- · Academic research guidance and code review for Bachelor and Master computer science students' final project.

# Bar-Ilan University, Department of Computer Science

July 2020 - July 2021

Research And Teaching Assistant

- · Teaching the following courses: Advanced Programming 1 and Advanced Programming 2.
- · Academic research guidance for Master computer science students' final project.

## ACADEMIC HONORS AND AWARDS

#### **Bar-Ilan University**

2017

M.Sc student

· A prize for excellence in studies and research at the master's degree in the name of David Barkovski.

## LIST OF PUBLICATIONS

#### Articles in Refereed Journals

1. **T. Lazebnik**, L. Shami, S. Bunimovich-Mendrazitsky, Spatio-Temporal Influence of Non-Pharmaceutical Interventions Policies on Pandemic Dynamics and the Economy: The Case of COVID-19. Economic Research-Ekonomska Istraživanja. 2021.

IF = 2.751; 0 citations.

2. **T. Lazebnik**, S. Bunimovich-Mendrazitsky, The signature features of COVID-19 pandemic in a hybrid mathematical model - implications for optimal work-school lockdown policy. Advanced Theory and Simulations. 2020.

IF = 2.951; 1 citations.

3. **T. Lazebnik**, S. Bunimovich-Mendrazitsky, PDE based geometry model for BCG immunotherapy of bladder cancer. Biosystems. 2020.

IF = 1.947; 1 citations.

4. **T. Lazebnik**, S. Yantez, S. Bunimovich-Mendrazitsky, N. Aaroni, Treatment of Bladder Cancer Using BCG Immunotherapy: PDE Modeling. Functional Differential Equations. 2019.

IF = No IF; 1 citations.

5. **T. Lazebnik**, S. Yantez, A Stable Algorithm for Numerical Matrix Exponent. Functional Differential Equations. 2017.

IF = No IF; 1 citations.

# Manuscripts Submitted / Under Review

- 1. **T. Lazebnik**, R. Rezni, Bunimovich-Mendrazitsky, A. Rosenfeld, Balancing Explainability-Performance Feature Selection Algorithm through Iterative Ensemble Intersections.
- 2. **T. Lazebnik**, S. Bunimovich-Mendrazitsky, Decision Tree Post-Pruning Without Loss Of Accuracy using the SAT-PP algorithm with An Empirical Evaluation on Clinical Data.
- 3. **T. Lazebnik**, S. Bunimovich-Mendrazitsky, Improved Geometric Configuration for the Bladder Cancer BCG-based Immunotherapy Treatment Model.
- 4. **T. Lazebnik**, S. Bunimovich-Mendrazitsky, A More Numerically Accurate Algorithm For Matrix Exponent.
- 5. **T. Lazebnik**, L. Shami, S. Bunimovich-Mendrazitsky, Pandemic Management by a Spatio-temporal Mathematical Model.

- 6. **T. Lazebnik**, S. Bunimovich-Mendrazitsky, L. Shaikhet, Novel Method to Analytically Obtain the Asymptotic Stable Equilibria States of Extended SIR-type Epidemiological Models.
- 7. **T. Lazebnik**, H. Weitman, Y. Goldberg, G. A. Kaminka, Rivendell: Project-Based Academic Search Engine.
- 8. **T. Lazebnik**, H. Weitman, G. A. Kaminka, Graph-Based Pharmacokinetics-Pharmadynamics Modeling for Large Scale Systems: Nanoparticles Case.
- 9. **T. Lazebnik**, Z. Bahouth, S. Bunimovich-Mendrazitsky, S. Halachmi, Predicting Acute Kidney Injury Following Open Partial Nephrectomy Treatment Using SAT-Pruned Explainable Machine Learning Model.
- 10. L. Shami, **T. Lazebnik**, Financing and Managing Epidemiological-Economic Crises: The Reserve Model.
- 11. S. Natan, T. Lazebnik, E. Lerner, A Distinction of Three Online Learning Pedagogic Paradigms.

### **Invited Talks**

1. **Subject:** Influence of Non-Pharmaceutical Interventions Policies on Pandemic Dynamics from Economic Prospective.

Location: Western Galilee College Economics Faculty Seminar, 2021.

2. Subject: PDE Modeling of Bladder Cancer Treatment Using BCG Immunotherapy.

Location: Functional Differential Equations conference, 2019.

3. Subject: A Stable Algorithm for Numerical Matrix Exponent.

Location: Bar-Ilan University Mathematics Faculty Seminar, 2017.

#### **LANGUAGES**

• Hebrew: Native.

• Russian: Native.

• English: Full professional proficiency.

#### RECOMMENDATIONS

- 1. Dr. Svetlana Bunimovich-Mendrazitsky, Senior Lecturer; Department of Mathematics, Ariel University. Email: svetlanabu@ariel.ac.il
- 2. Prof. Gal A. Kaminka, Senior Lecturer and Head of the Computer Science Department, Bar-Ilan University. Email: galk@cs.biu.ac.il
- 3. Dr. Hana Weitman, Library Manager; Department of Computer Science, Bar-Ilan University. Email: weitman@mail.biu.ac.il
- 4. Dr. Labib Shami, Senior Lecturer; Department of Economics, Western Galilee College. Email: labibs@wgalil.ac.il
- 5. Prof. Avi Rosenfeld, Senior Lecturer; Department of Computer Science, Jerusalem College of Technology. Email: rosenfa@gmail.com
- 6. Dr. Asaf Tzachor, Research Associate; Centre For The Of Existential Risk, University of Cambridge. Email: asaf.tz@gmail.com